const quizDataEsp = [
    {
        question: 'nosotros | comer',
        1: 'como',
        2: 'come',
        3: 'comemos',
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'ustedes | comprender',
        1: 'comprendo',
        2: 'comprendéis',
        3: 'comprenden',
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'vosotras | leer',
        1: 'leemos',
        2: 'leéis',
        3: 'leen',
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'yo | ver',
        1: 've',
        2: 'vemos',
        3: 'veo',
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'vosotros| aprender',
        1: 'aprendes',
        2: 'aprendéis',
        3: 'aprenden',
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'nosotras| beber',
        1: 'bebemos',
        2: 'bebéis',
        3: 'beben',
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'ella | correr',
        1: 'corremos',
        2: 'corre',
        3: 'corro',
        correct: 2
    }
    /*
    ,
    {
        question: 'él | ',
        1: '',
        2: '',
        3: '',
        correct:
    },
    {
        question: 'tú |',
        1: '',
        2: '',
        3: '',
        correct:
    },
    {
        question: 'usted |',
        1: '',
        2: '',
        3: '',
        correct:
    }
    */
]